<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data>
  <content>
    <quote>This work is absolutely phenomenal !!!!  You guys are awesome...  We are very, very pleased and look forward to working with you guys on other projects."</quote>
    <name>Ralph Donaldson Jr.- WiseThink Health</name>
  </content>
  <content>
    <quote>I love it.. Looks great. You guys do great work and Chantel is beautiful. I and my boss are impressed. We have several others we want you to do for us."</quote>
    <name>Dan Cusack- Superior Surgical, LLC</name>
  </content>
  <content>
    <quote>I just wanted to give KUDOS to the production of the latest video made on www.hafha.com...I love the way it was made and how it is displayed on the site."</quote>
    <name>Marty- Virginia Homes</name>
  </content>
  <content>
    <quote>Please get that on our website immediately! Love it, love it, love it! Awesome job to everyone involved!! ... I will absolutely be sending more clients your way!"</quote>
    <name>Derek- PC Austin</name>
  </content>
  <content>
    <quote>I really appreciate your wonderful assistance and expertise here.  Working with you guys continues to be excellent.  Thanks again."</quote>
    <name>Sean Childs- Horizon Marketing Group</name>
  </content>
  <content>
    <quote>Excellent!  Great job, and excellent turn-around.  You will definitely be hearing from us again.  Thanks!"</quote>
    <name>Rick Lamberson- BlueWater Inet Group</name>
  </content>
  <content>
    <quote>Excellent!  Installed in just   seconds and works great!"</quote>
    <name>Thomas Kain- Dealer World</name>
  </content>
  <content>
    <quote>I had an exceptionally tight deadline... WebsiteTalkingHeads\xae went above and beyond to ensure my project was completed on time."</quote>
    <name>Benjamin Croft- WBECS</name>
  </content>
  <content>
    <quote>It was sincerely my pleasure in doing business with you.  Refreshing in having your "Customer Service" ... so Prompt and Accurate!!!"</quote>
    <name>Mike Svestka- Printing Industry Exchange</name>
  </content>
  <content>
    <quote>Thanks so much for the GREAT customer service.  You guys were prompt in the order process; quick to respond to emails, and cordial over the Phone."</quote>
    <name>Tim and Greg- Rainbow RV</name>
  </content>
  <content>
    <quote>I could not be happier with the product, with your service, and with your company.  I hope to need your services many more times! Thanks a million!"</quote>
    <name>Kevin Ramsey- Urban Cards and Comics</name>
  </content>
  <content>
    <quote>Guys this is so cool, you did a great job.  Thanks, more than I could hope for, but just what I wanted.  We will work together again, count on it"</quote>
    <name>Gabriel McCrea- Search Corp</name>
  </content>
  <content>
    <quote>Thank you very much! The video looks absolutely wonderful and meets our   expectations 100% - this is a great job. Please convey my thanks to the team and   Chantel."</quote>
    <name>Damith Perera- SEOLIX</name>
  </content>
</data>
